Bob Considine Papers
Bob Considine Papers
- Recordings
  - Audiorecordings
    - [Untitled], considine_b_022; accompanied by postage label from Recording International Inc. to Bob Considine; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 5)
  - Films
    - Cavanaugh film, Sportsmen, Inc., considine_b_027; accompanied by photocopy of the old label: "75 reel, 75, can. Property of Sportsmen, Inc. Brattleboro, Vt."; Film: 16mm
    - NBC TV, News and Special Events present: On the Line with Bob Considine, considine_b_026; accompanied by photocopy of the old label: "Charley Company 16mm Considine". Film credits: Dennis Daton, Editor, Thomas Galvin, Editor, Martin Hoade, Director; Film: 16mm